costumecraze.com 2017-06-06

# Costume Craze Privacy Policy | Costume Craze

## Bottom Line Privacy Policy:

All information you provide is confidential. Your information will not be given away, sold, or shared except in pursuit of fulfilling your order.

## And now, you can read the extended version:

Costume Craze is committed to protecting your privacy, and otherwise providing a safe environment for you to shop. We want you to be aware of the information we collect (and do not collect) and how it is we protect your information while ordering at Costume Craze. As such, we have created the following "Privacy Policy," which we invite you to read over carefully (along with our "Terms & Conditions" notice).

Privacy of children is of the utmost importance to Costume Craze. We do not knowingly market or sell goods to children under the age of 13. Nor do we knowingly collect personal information of children under the age of 13. In the rare case that we discover we have unintentionally collected such information, immediate action will be taken--including, but not limited to, deleting such records from our database(s), and pursuing any further action, as deemed necessary, to ensure that privacy is protected.

When placing an order (whether through our website, www.costumecraze.com, or via phone), Costume Craze collects such information as your name, email address, phone number, mailing and/or billing address, etc. This information is collected for the sole purpose of completing your order and is only shared with direct fulfillment partners (such as bank and credit card partners, shipping partners, etc.). It is never shared, sold, or otherwise distributed to third parties not directly associated with the fulfillment of your order.

Furthermore, Costume Craze uses the latest encryption technology to insure all transmissions of sensitive information over the Internet are done securely. Costume Craze is an authenticated SSL secure site.

Costume Craze may contact you regarding your order either by phone or through email. It is important that the information you provide at checkout is complete and accurate, so we can contact you about your order (including an official receipt of your purchase with us, tracking details of your package, etc.). Additionally, Costume Craze may contact you via email about general announcements, including but not limited to sales or other special offers, contests, survey solicitations, etc. Unlike communications relating directly to your order, communications of this nature are completely optional, and you may choose to opt out of these solicitations at any time by simply clicking a link you will find in those emails.

Costume Craze has engaged one or more third party partners to track usage on the Costume Craze website (www.costumecraze.com), including information about your visit and your browsing and buying habits at www.costumecraze.com. Collected data may also provide information on the effectiveness of Costume Craze marketing campaigns appearing on other websites. _This data is anonymous and exclusively meant for statistical treatment._ Costume Craze does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third party partners.

Costume Craze may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. In such an event, Costume Craze will either notify you via email and/or place a prominent notice on our website.

Questions? Comments? We'd love to hear from you!

## Email: 

## Phone: 

888-922-7293 or (801) 796-1053

## Mailing Address:

Costume Craze, LLC  
350 West Center Street  
Pleasant Grove, UT 84062
